其方が負けたら 左腕をもらう。
Fearsome monsters... Exotic creatures...
えっとですね 左腕ではなくてですね
Vast riches... Hidden treasures...
いつも　ワダすが 賭けているものではダメですか？ 何だと？　何をだ。
Evil enclaves... Unexplored lands...
命です。
The word "unknown" holds magic.
命か。 どうやら　覚悟が 足りなかったのは　余のほうだ。
And some incredible people are
drawn to that magic. They are known...
これで許せ。
...as Hunters!
ネフェルピトーは　王の傷を 治療するために「円」を解き
when you're able to punch me
in the face, just like that.
ノヴは　その隙を突いて 宮殿内へ進入した
Until then, I shall leave the tag with you.
とうとう来た　ここまで
Trap x In The x Hole
ハァ　ハァ　ハァ　ハァ…。 中央階段までは まだ１００ｍ以上…
Gon was humiliated, after Hisoka recovered the tags
taken by Gerreta.
ハァ　ハァ　ハァ…。
As for Killua...
ふぅ…。
You're wasting your time. I'll never give you an opening to attack.
奇妙な樹木に 巨大な実がなっている
Tremble with fear. Wear yourself out.
１本の木に　５００はあろうか
I am a very cautious man.
それが１０本 ということは５０００
I go to any lengths necessary, even when facing a child.
一日で５０万人が選別され 約１％が選別に耐え　生き残る
Once he exhausts himself,
and has no choice but to sleep, I'll attack!
その計画が１日しか実行されず 中断しているから　計算は合う
I am a very cautious man. Man...
これは　選別された人間の繭
If you're not gonna show yourself,
I'll come to you. Huh?
かえれば 念能力を持つ人間兵器として
What a pain...
王の手先となり　人類に牙をむく
You're only worth one point to me.
この兵隊を 王の意のままに操り
He wants to fight? I can't possibly lose, right?
侵略を 全世界へ拡大する気だろう
He's just a kid.
させてたまるか！
Why is he so calm?
まずは「遠い出口」　設置完了
Is he really that strong? Right... I am a very cautious man.
次は　もっと近く
I should esca—
宮殿の入口
I mean, I should back off. But...
辺りも　随分　暗くなって来た
My brothers will yell at me!
順調
Actually, if I go back without
taking his tag, they'll definitely yell at me!
「中間の出口」　設置完了
Bro!
次は　「近い出口」
We ran into some trouble. You're done, right?
恐らく　中にいるのは 最小限の構成員
You idiot!
行ける！ ここまで来れば　宮殿内部も
You can't even beat a little kid?
玉座は　宮殿の３階中央奥
Y-You got it wrong, Amo! What do I have wrong?
コンマ１秒でも 護衛軍の判断時間を奪いたい
I-I didn't want to hurt a little kid. So I figured I'd take it while he slept.
そのためには　１階では遠い
You're lying through your teeth!
２階の中央階段　ここがベスト
F-Fine! If you insist, that leaves me no choice.
あの中庭を越えれば その先に中央階段が…
If I start to lose, my brothers will come to my aid.
保険のため ここにも出口を作っておくか
Huh? What? Did you go easy on him?
いや　ここじゃ　外と大差ない
You're too nice, Imori. Y-Yeah...
せめて　１階の中央階段のそば
#198, huh?
できれば　階段を上り２階へ
What? No way... Since it's only a number off
from the one I'm after, maybe #199 is one of your two buddies?
「スクリーム」
Umori... Yeah.
閉じろ
Get in formation. Time to get serious.
他に仲間はいたか？
It doesn't matter how strong he is. He stands no chance
against our teamwork.
見られていたら　万事休す
We three have
撤退しか…
defeated many tough opponents
with this formation. Just you wait...
ふぅ…。 １匹で行動していたのか
A-Above?
ハァ　ハァ…。
Hey. Are you #199? Yeah...
無理だ
And the other one goes this way.
何だ？　あのオーラは
You still have three days.
この世の　あらゆる不吉を はらんでいるよう
Good luck finding them. See ya.
いや 今更　死ぬことは怖くない 最も怖いのは この上にいる奴らは
Damn it!
そう確信できるほど 濃いオーラ ここが限界…
#197 was always accompanied by #199...
ん？
The kid noticed I was there...
誰かと思えば テレビに出てた獅子男か。 覚えておけ　俺の名はレオルだ。
Man, that was boring.
新手は　ザリガニとオオカミって 聞いてたんだけどなぁ。
Wonder what Gon's doing.
奴らは　お前の作った 雑魚どもを始末してる。 俺とタイマンはれるようにな。
Hunter Vocabulary
そいつは　また　ご苦労なこった。
Too Bad
できるだけ　敵の目を 引きつけておくしかねえ
Six days have passed.
フン！　無駄なことを。
Only one day left... It's been four days since
we ran into Hisoka.
食料の搬入だな
Well? Anyone there?
マルコスの情報が正しければ
No one that can be easily spotted.
あの中に 生きた女性が含まれている 王にではなく 好色家　ビゼフ長官への貢ぎ物
Damn... Perhaps we should split up to search, after we decide on a time and
place to reconvene.
作戦が成功していれば パームも　あの中に
It'll go faster with three people.
４号車は　そのままでいい。
I see... We should search from above. That won't work.
はっ。
It's only possible if you have eyes
as sharp as Gon's.
では　我々は失礼します。
Gon. Huh?
うん。
Do you have the tags you need?
舞台は天空闘技場
Damn, so I'm the only one
without enough points. Who's your target?
黒ずくめの武装集団が 襲って来て… ハンターに死を。
#246, a woman named Ponzu.
昔　ネテロ会長と一緒に 戦っていた仲間だったらしい
I heard that she uses chemical weapons.
ネテロ この恨み　決して忘れんぞ！
Gon, did you see any women
when you were up there?
前売り券プレゼントに同封の 応募ハガキで…
Nope. I see.
フフフフ…。
We can assume that there
are four possibilities.
欲しい！ これは　レアアイテムだな
She's in good shape,
and she still has her tag. She's in good shape,
but she's lost her tag.
フフフフっ。
If she were caught in a sudden accident, or if she were defeated after
hiding the tag.
地下格納庫エリアＤ 誰にも邪魔されない 俺のパラダイス
If she died after concealing her tag, we won't be able to find it.
さぁ　出たまえ　心配はいらない。
She's known for using drugs, right? Some of them must have strong scents.
何とかして ここを抜け出して
Yep, definitely. What do you want to do?
王と護衛軍を　この目で見る！
I'm going inside.
パームは　自らの目で見た者の 現在の動向を
You guys, wait here.
一番大事なのは 絶対に成功することじゃなく
There don't appear to be any traps.
失敗した時　捕まった時に
I'll head inside.
速やかに死ぬこと！
Don't enter until I give the okay.
ハァ　ハァ　ハァ…。
If that happens, you guys
should return to the start. I can't do that.
ハァ　ハァ　ハァ　ハァ…。 ハァ　ハァ　ハァ…。
Since we've teamed up, I won't abandon you now. Then I quit the team.
ここまで来れば　安全 ハァ…。
It's selfish, considering all the
help you've given me, but I'll do this alone.
パーム　絶対に無理はするな
Still got a problem?
お前が成功しなくても 計画は　もう実行できる
Do whatever you want.
あんな　あんな… 凶暴なオーラ…
Hold onto that for me.
お前達も 奴らのオーラを見てんだよな
I have to go for it...
仲間を救うため？
Isn't that...
人類を守るため？
Bourbon? I'm guessing that
なぜ　まだ戦えるんだ？
I'm your target? Ponzu!
パーム！
There's no point. We gain nothing by fighting here.
無理は　やめてくれ
It's just as you said...
捕まれば　全てが終わる
You're my target!
パーム！
Let's pretend that a miracle occurs, and you defeat me.
俺は　もう そこへは行けない…
You still won't be able
to leave this cave. What? What do you mean?
フフフ。
Is Leorio okay? Yeah.
君は　もういい 個室で待機していたまえ。
It's been nearly thirty minutes.
はい。
Kurapika! Gon!
少々　出来過ぎだがな。
Leorio!
ここは　有事の際に 防空壕としても使われる。
You fools... Why did you enter the cave?
暴れて死ぬには　最適の場所だ。
He has bites all over his body! If those snakes were venomous...
まぁ　念仏は セルフサービスでやってくれや。
They're vipers. Their poison isn't that strong.
俺は無神論者なんでな。 フッ！　楽観的な野郎だな。
But he's been bitten
too many times!
追い詰められたのは　どっちか 見せてやるよ
S-Stop it!
フゥ。
If you have any cavities or
open wounds in your mouth...
フン。 ヂートゥから聞いてるぜ。
If I did, I could have saved you guys...
そいつを　いろんなもんに 変えられるらしいじゃねえか。
Leorio! Anyway, we have to stop the bleeding.
知った上で ここへ誘導したってか
Uh-huh!
思い通りに 事が運んでいるつもりの奴は 惜し気なく 自分の能力を見せてくれるから
That should do it. We need to take him to a doctor!
だが　まだ お目にかかったことはねえ
I would stop if I were you.
俺の「ディープパープル」より
You cannot leave.
対応力のある 能力の持ち主にはな
What do you mean?
ピリピリ来るねぇ　いい感じだ 互いが てめぇの能力を出し合う瞬間 やめられねえな
When someone tries to exit this cave, snakes attack them.
敵が能力を出す前に たたけってのは正論さ
Bourbon, the snake charmer,
set this trap.
だが　そんなもんじゃねえだろ 男の戦ってのはよ
If you're bitten, you'll end up paralyzed like he is.
おいおい　何のまねだ？
Bourbon!
自ら五感の１つを縛るのかい？
You're looking for tags, right? We'll give you every tag
in our possession.
「ブラックプラネット」ってバンド 知ってるかい？
So let us out of here!
こいつらのセカンドアルバムが 超クールでよ。 全１２曲だが　連作になっててな
It's no use. He's already dead.
心地いい浮遊感が残るんだ。 知ってるよ。
D-Dead?
名盤だ！
Gon and his friends have
been caught in Bourbon
悔しいが同感だな。
the snake charmer's trap,
and can't leave the cave.
レンタル　スタート！ まじぃな…
Will Leorio survive the
venomous snake bites?